JAKUB KOPTA



+48 888 446 325

✓ jakubkopta@gmail.com

Q Cracow, Poland

github.com/jakubkopta

PROFILE

I am a third-year student of Automatics and Robotics at AGH in Cracow. I am open to new experience and enjoy learning new things. As someone taking their first steps in the IT industry, I would like to develop my skills in this area.

SKILLS

- Java 8+
- React
- MySQL
- JavaScript and TypeScript
- Spring
- Git, Maven
- HTML/CSS
- Python basics
- Teamwork and Problem-Solving
- English B2
- Driver's license cat. B, B+E

COURSES

JAVA DEVELOPER

Coders Lab

16.07.2022 - 19.02.2023

SCRUM LAB JAVA

Coders Lab

06.11.2022 - 18.11.2022

BASICS OF HTML AND CSS

Coders Lab

04.2022

EDUCATION

AGH UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY IN CRACOW

Automatics and Robotics

Faculty of Electrical Engineering, Automatics, Computer Science and Biomedical Engineering

2020 - current

4TH GENERAL HIGH SCHOOL

Mathematics, Physics, Computer Science, English

2016 - 2019

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR DRIVER

Good Lood

01.2020 - 06.2020 Driver

06.2020 - 10.2020 Trainer

10.2020 - 01.2023 Senior Driver

- Coordinating team work
- Training new employees
- Taking care of vehicle technical codnition

INTRESTS

- Mountain biking
- Snowboarding
- Sailing

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).